# Joaquin Morales Jr

■ Joaquinmorales5613@gmail.com

**L** 214-518-1437

O Dallas, TX

in linkedin.com/in/joaquin-morales-046a12183 🕥 github.com/Joaquin95

## PROFILE

Completed a full-stack software developer program, learning front-end and back-end technologies to develop user-focused web applications. I designed applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and React.js, improving user engagement and implemented RESTful APIs to enhance performance and user experience.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

02/2024 - present Dallas, Tx

## The Mortgage Calculator

Mortgage Loan Originator

- Engage with consumers, determine their needs, and offer the appropriate products.
- Explain complex mortgage concepts to clients in a clear and concise manner.
- Proficient in encompass Software and CRM systems to manage client information and track loan progress.
- Build and maintain strong relationships with real estate agents, builders, and other professionals in the industry.

07/2022 - 01/2024 Dallas, Tx

#### Scavuzzos

Truck Driver

- · Consistently achieved on-time deliveries by effectively coordinating with restaurant managers and transportation teams, resulting client satisfaction.
- Cultivated a professional image while on the road, contributing to a positive company reputation and fostering trust with clients.
- · Conducted regular inspections of the vehicle, promptly reporting road hazards and safety concerns to the transportation manager, thereby minimizing risks and ensuring safe travel for all deliveries.

### **EDUCATION**

08/2024 - 12/2024 Certification

4Geeks Academy

Full Stack Software Developer

08/2009 - 06/2013

**Diploma** 

Dallas, United States

Skyline high School

02/2021 - present

**Computer Science** Richland College

Dallas, Tx

#### SKILLS

• HTML

CSS

JavaScript

• GitHub

• Node.js

• RESTful APIs

Python

Microsoft Word, Excel, and PP

· React.js

## **ANGUAGES**

Spanish

. . . . .